Kevin Le

Software Engineering & Cloud Technology Graduate Perth, Western Australia

My ambition is to utilise technology and innovative ideas to deliver excellent outcomes that positively impact people. I have experience working in Azure and AWS cloud environments building on various frameworks to deliver secure, performant, and worthwhile outcomes that create value for the business and its customers.

Education

Curtin University Bentley, Western Australia

Bachelor of Science (Computing) - Software Engineering

2018 - 2020

- Course Weighted Average: 82.44%
- Achievements: Vice Chancellors List 2020 Semester 1 (Top 1% of University)

Dean of Science Commendation Semester 1, 2 2019, Semester 1, 2 2020

Chisholm Catholic College

Bedford, Western Australia

2013 - 2017

- ATAR: 81.5
- Achieved Certificate II Creative Industries (Media) CUA202125

Experience

WACE

HBF Health Perth, Western Australia

Graduate - Cloud Based Technology

February 2021 - Current

- Support HBF in embedding a culture of effective technology use through cloud services awareness.
- Help identify, assess, propose, and implement solutions relating to cloud technology opportunities.
- Work collaboratively with key stakeholders, partners, and teams to drive the right delivery outcomes.
- Provide specialist support and advice on the implementation of a cloud software solution.

KH Garage Doors Malaga, Western Australia

Assistant

February 2014 - December 2019

- Managed invoice creation and bookkeeping.
- Developed a program to automatically generate invoices using LaTeX, Python and React saving man-hours. Previously invoices manually typed.
- Assisted with door repairs and installation.

MCQ Supermarkets

Systems Administrator

Beechboro, Western Australia August 2016 - September 2018

- Provided systems administration consisting of email server management, managing stock take software, and maintenance/reliability checks of security systems.
- Learnt to adapt my communication style to suit client's level of technical expertise.
- Developed a strong understanding of Windows systems administration, use of financial software and understanding client needs.
- Handled confidential company information professionally and with absolute integrity.

Skills

Programming Languages: C, C#, HTML, Java, JavaScript, MySQL, PHP, Python, R

Technologies & Frameworks: Adobe Creative Suite, Amazon Web Services, Android Studio, Azure, Azure DevOps, Cisco

iOS, DaVinci Resolve, Git, Django, Grafana, LaTeX, Microsoft Office, Nmap, React, Shodan,

Solidworks, Unix, Wireshark, Xamarin, .NET Core, Vue,

Languages: English (Native), Vietnamese (Full Professional Proficiency)